Jose Perez

6419 Dwightware Blvd Charlotte, NC 28227 (980) 253-4981 Joseperez940@live.com

OBJECTIVE

As a Road-To-Hire Graduate and an individual with experience in the workforce I've become intrigued to expand my journey into the world of technology and grow from within. With customer service experience knowing how important the needs of clients are to meeting quotas and making partners happy with result driven goals. I have made the best of my abilities in all positions I've been a part of and hope to continue my growth.

QUALIFICATIONS

Understanding of Front End & Back End technologies (HTML, CSS, Javascript, Go, etc., Professional Development Skills. Business Communications I & II, Business Math, Keyboarding I & II, Written Communications, Professional Development, Physical Geography, Literature, Psychology, Economics, Public Speaking

EXPERIENCE

RGX Rim Repair, Charlotte, NC - Rim Technician

JANUARY 2019 - JANUARY 2020

• Repair/Recondition Customer Auto Rims to original finish

Service Pros Installation Group, Charlotte,NC - Scheduling Coordinator/Customer Care Specialist

DECEMBER 2016- DECEMBER 2018

Contact customer to update/follow up/schedule throughout installation process

Telenetwork , Charlotte, NC(At-Home) - Tech Support Representative

AUGUST 2016 - DECEMBER 2016

 Handle incoming calls from residential TV/Internet customers to troubleshoot technical problems.

Global Linking Service , Charlotte, NC) - Network Operation Center Technician

NOVEMBER 2014 - JULY 2015

• Monitor clients networks for any faults, diagnose issues, dispatch for onsite support

EDUCATION

Road to Hire Coding Fellowship, Fort Mill, SC - Technology Fellow

JANUARY 2020 - PRESENT

- Front End & Back End Technologies(HTML, CSS, JS, Go, etc)
- Professional Development

King's College, Charlotte, NC - A.A.S Network Management

SEPTEMBER 2013 - DECEMBER 2014

Independence High School, Charlotte, NC - High School Diploma

AUGUST 2010 - JUNE 2013